which is the basis of this We we have
from a bourgeois point of view, not least talked about
integration in terms of paying
tax and is self-sufficient but that
says nothing and what values
But uh No but my answer is Eh I think
actually not that I don't know Therefore
that I think this way that the question is about
that's really the thing about inbred man
want to access or about this or about
it's honor culture or if it's just
that we think it's very screwed up
to marry their cousins ​​this spring
culture and if we just start with this one
rules on all citizens of Sweden and
that we don't just look between our fingers
because they happen to have a Muslim one
surname eh Some of the criticism has
been that this proposal risks that
after all, like a function to fill but we
after all, other situations also have history
with coffee girls and turning pages and eh
posts in the wolf debate and such as me
think have been less successful Then want